pioneerdj.com 2019-04-18

# Privacy policy - Pioneer DJ - Global

**Last Updated:** June 2018 ("Effective Date")

This website Privacy Policy is brought to you by Pioneer DJ Corporation. We take the privacy of our website users very seriously to ensure your rights and freedoms are protected. We ask that you read this Privacy Policy carefully as it contains important information about how we will use your personal data.

Pioneer DJ Corporation, ("we" or "us") is the "data controller" (ie the company who is responsible for, and controls the processing of, your personal data), and how we will meet our data protection obligations and Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations (“PECR”).

As we are based outside the European Economic Area, we have nominated the following representative:

Pioneer DJ Europe Ltd, Artemis Building, Odyssey Business Park, West End Road, South Ruislip, Middlesex, HA4 6QE, United Kingdom. Telephone number [+44 (0)203 761 7220](tel:00442037617220)

This Privacy Policy applies to the information that we obtain through your use of Pioneer DJ website including any microsites (Each, "Website," and collectively, "Websites"), mobile app, and associated web-based services (collectively "Services"). Your privacy matters to us so please take the time to familiarize yourself with our policies and the ways in which you can protect your privacy. lf you have any questions, please contact us at [privacy@pioneerdj.com](mailto:privacy@pioneerdj.com). This policy is incorporated into and is subject to the Terms of Service Agreement and License Agreement [kuvo.com](http://kuvo.com/terms/)

This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected by us offline or through any other means; or by any third party, including through any third-party content (i.e. advertising that may link or be accessible from or on the Services).

### Information We Collect

#### Information you provide to us

We collect the following information:

##### Account and Profile Information

We collect information about you when you register for an account and create or modify your profile on the Services. lnformation we collect may include your account name, username, email address, birth year, password, profile photo, and whether you are a DJ.

We also collect information you choose to include in your biography and news updates on your profile. For clubs, we also collect address and phone number.

##### Content

Our mobile app allows you to take photos. These photos are stored on your mobile device and not transferred to or stored by us in any other locations. lf you are a DJ, we also receive information about the tracks you play using our product.

##### Other submissions

We collect other data that you may submit to our Services or us directly, such as when you request customer support or communicate with us via email or social media sites.

#### Information we collect from your use of our Services

##### Usage Data, Web Logs, and Analytics Information

We record certain information and store it in log files when you interact with our Services. We collect information about your interactions with the Service, including which clubbers, playlists, tracks, clubs, and DJs you follow or like. We also collect technical data such as internet protocol (lP) address, MAC address, or other device addresses or identifiers, as well as browser type, internet service provider, URLs of referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and your mobile carrier. We and our analytics providers also collect and store analytics information when you use our Services to help us improve our Services.

##### Location Information

We collect and store your location information if your device and/or web browser settings are enabled to send it to us and, where required by applicable law, if you have provided prior consent; where we believe it is necessary for our legitimate interests, or where you have agreed to our terms of use. lf you do not allow collection of this information; some aspects of the Services may not be available.

##### Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

We use various technologies to collect information, including cookies that we save to your computer or mobile device. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive or in device memory. We use cookies to improve and customize our Services and your experience; to allow you to access and use the Services without re-entering your username or password; and to count visits and understand which areas and features of the Services are most popular. We may also associate the information we store in cookies with information you submit while on our Services. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from websites you visit. lf you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all aspects of our Services. Please also see our Cookies Policy. Anonymous session information is collected and analyzed by Google LLC using Google Analytics. For more information about google, Google's use of cookies, and Google's privacy practice, please click here: [www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/)

We use pixel services run by third parties, including without limitation Amazon.com. These third parties place and use pixels that collect data about visitors interacting with our Services to provide measurement services and show interest-based ads to the visitors on sites across the Internet. These third parties are responsible for the data collection. Information about how you can opt out of receiving Amazon interest-based ads is found on this site: <https://www.amazon.com/adprefs>. You can opt out of receiving interest-based ads from third parties who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative here: <http://optout.networkadvertising.org/?c=1#!/>. You can opt out of receiving interest-based ads from third parties who follow the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles here: [http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN.](http://optout.aboutads.info/?c=2&lang=EN)

#### Information we collect from other sources

##### Other Services

You can access or register for the Services using your account credentials for third party services (each, an "lntegrated Service") such as Twitter or Facebook, or otherwise connect such lntegrated Services to your account. By connecting with an lntegrated Service, you authorize us to access and store your name, email address, date of birth, gender, current city, profile picture URL, comments, and other information that the Integrated Service makes available to us, and to use and disclose it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. You should review your privacy settings on each lntegrated Service to understand the information sent to us through each lntegrated Service. Please review each lntegrated Service's terms of use and privacy policies carefully before using their services and connecting to our Services.

##### Information from third party services:

We may obtain information from third parties such as our partners and service providers, and combine it with other information we collect from you.

### How We Use Information We Collect

We may use the information we collect for a variety of purposes, including to:

  * Contact you to ensure that our records of your personal information are correct;
  * Provide, operate, maintain, improve, personalize, and promote our Services;
  * Enable you to access and use our Services; 
  * Communicate with you, including responding to your comments, questions, and requests; complaints; providing customer service and support; providing you with information about services, including technical notices, updates, security alerts, administrative messages, or advertising or marketing messages; and providing other news or information about us;
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage, and activities in connection with our Services; and lnvestigate and prevent unauthorized access to our Services and other illegal activities;
  * We may also use the information we collect for other purposes about which we notify you. 
  * With your permission, we may also use your email address to send you commercial messages, including changes to your products or news related to Pioneer DJ. lf you no longer wish to receive marketing messages, from us or our third party partners, you may opt out at any time. Opting out may prevent you from receiving messages regarding improvements or new services.

We will not keep your personal data for longer than we need it for our legitimate purpose and shall take into account the following when determining the appropriate retention period for keeping your personal data:

  * the amount, nature, and sensitivity of your personal data;
  * the risk of harm from unauthorised use or disclosure;
  * the purposes for which we process your personal data and how long we need the particular data to achieve these purposes; and
  * how long the personal data is likely to remain accurate and up to date.

### Information Sharing and Disclosures

We may share your information in the following ways:

##### Your consent

We will share your personal information with companies, organizations, or individuals outside of us when we have your consent to do so.

##### Your use

When you use our Services, your profile, news updates, comments, favorites, likes, followers, and, if you are a DJ, your playlists and gig histories are viewable by the public and other users by default. You can change your profile settings at any time to make your information private and not viewable by the public or other users on our Website as described below. We urge you to consider the sensitivity of any information prior to sharing it publicly.

##### Social Networking and Other Websites.

Our Services may allow you to share information, including photos, tracks, playlist information, and other personal information with social networking websites such as Facebook and Twitter. lf you provide comments on our Website using integrated social networking services, your comments will be shared on those services. Their use of the information will be governed by their privacy policies.

##### Service Providers

We may share your information with service providers that perform services on our behalf. We authorize service providers to use or disclose personal information only as necessary to perform certain services on our behalf or comply with legal requirements. We require them to appropriately safeguard the privacy and security of personal information they process on our behalf.

##### Third Party Partners:

We may share your information with third party partners such as analytics and advertising partners to provide services such as analytics and online advertising. Our partners may collect information about your online activities over time and across different online services when you use our Services. We may share information with our partners for marketing purposes, including for their direct marketing purposes.

##### Aggregate Data

We may share aggregate information that does not identify you with third parties.

##### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Our Rights:

We may disclose your information (including your personal information) to a third party if (a) we believe that disclosure is reasonably necessary to comply with any applicable law, regulation, legal process or governmental request, (b) to enforce our agreements, policies and terms of service, (c) to protect the security or integrity of Pioneer DJ's products and services, (d) to protect the property, rights, and safety of Pioneer DJ, our customers or the public from harm or illegal activities, (e) to respond to an emergency which we believe in the good faith requires us to disclose information to assist in preventing the death or serious bodily injury of any person, or (f) to investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations.

##### Business Transfers

We may share or transfer your information (including your personal information) in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company. We will notify you of such a change in ownership or transfer of assets by posting a notice on our website.

### Your Choices and Privacy Settings 

You may decline to share certain personal information with us, in which case we may not be able to provide to you some of the features and functionality of our Services.

Subject to applicable law, you may have the right to request access to and receive information about the personal information we maintain about you, update and correct inaccuracies in your personal information, and have the information blocked or deleted, as appropriate. The right to access personal information may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements.

We give you several methods to access, correct, update or request blocking or deletion of your personal information including:

  * You may access, update or correct certain personal information and privacy settings at any time by accessing the account settings section in your profile page on our Websites or mobile app.
  * You can also close your account through the account settings section and your personal information will no longer be viewable to other users.
  * You may exercise your rights by contacting us at the address below.

You may choose to keep your profile private through your account settings. lf you mark your profile or other information as private, we will still receive information about your profile and tracks, but they will not be viewable by other users.

You may opt out of receiving promotional communications from our Websites (including communications from third party partners) by using the unsubscribe link within each email or updating your email preferences in your account settings. Even after you opt out of receiving promotional messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative and security messages from us regarding the Services.

##### Notice to California residents

Pursuant to California Civil Code Section 1798.83, residents of the State of California have the right to request from companies conducting business in California certain information regarding disclosure within the immediately preceding calendar year of that California resident's personal information to third parties (and in some cases affiliates) for their direct marketing purposes. Alternatively, the law provides that a company may comply, as we do, by disclosing in its privacy policy that we provide consumers with a choice (opt-out or opt-in) regarding sharing personal information with third parties and affiliates for those third parties' and affiliates' direct marketing purposes, and information on how to exercise that choice. At this time, we do not share personally identifiable information with third parties or affiliates for those third parties' or affiliates' direct marketing purposes. lf we do so in the future, we will provide you with a choice prior to sharing your personally identifiable information with third parties and affiliates for their direct marketing purposes. lf you do not opt-in or if you choose to opt-out at the time we offer that choice, we will not share your information with that identified third party or affiliate for its direct marketing purposes.

##### Note to EEA residents

You have the right to request access to personal data that we may process about you. lf you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * put your request in writing;
  * include proof of your identity and address (eg a copy of your driving licence or passport, and a recent utility or credit card bill); and
  * specify the personal data you want access to, including any account or reference numbers where applicable.

We shall provide a copy of the personal data we process. However, for any further copies requested by you, we may charge a reasonable fee for the administration costs.

You have the right to require us to correct any inaccuracies in your data free of charge. If you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * put your request in writing;
  * provide us with enough information to identify you (eg account number, user name, registration details); and
  * specify the information that is incorrect and what it should be replaced with.

You also have the right to ask us to stop processing your personal data for direct marketing purposes. lf you wish to exercise this right, you should:

  * put your request in writing (an email sent to [exec.eu@pioneerdj.com](mailto:exec.eu@pioneerdj.com) with a header that says 'Unsubscribe' is acceptable);
  * provide us with enough information to identify you (eg account number, user name, registration details); and
  * if your objection is not to direct marketing in general, but to direct marketing by a particular channel (eg email or telephone), please specify the channel you are objecting to.

##### Do-Not-Track Signals

Because there is not yet a consensus on how companies should respond to web browser-based or other "Do Not Track" ("DNT") mechanisms, we currently do not respond to web browser DNT signals that provide a method to opt out of the collection of information about online activities over time and across third-party websites or online services. We may revisit our policy on responding to these signals, in which case we will post a revised privacy policy on this site.

##### Data Security

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. We maintain reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect the personal information you provide against accidental, unlawful or unauthorized destruction, loss, alteration, access, disclosure or use.

Unfortunately, the lnternet cannot be guaranteed to be 100% secure, and we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or store on the Services.

##### Children's Privacy

Our Services are not directed to individuals under 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. lf we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we will take steps to delete such information. lf you become aware that a child has provided us with personal information, please contact us at [privacy@pioneerdj.com](mailto:privacy@pioneerdj.com).

##### Third-Party Services

Our Services may contain features or links to web sites and services provided by third parties, including services that facilitate the purchase of songs and music albums. Any information you provide on third-party sites or services is provided directly to the operators of such sites or services and is subject to those operators' policies, if any, governing privacy and security, even if accessed through the Services. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided. We encourage you to learn about third parties' privacy and security policies before providing them with information.

##### International users

We may transfer the personal information we collect about you to countries other than the country in which it was originally collected. Those countries may not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the personal information. When we transfer your personal information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

lf you are located in the European Economic Area, we comply with applicable legal requirements for the transfer of personal information outside of the country of collection. By providing your personal information or using our Services, you consent to any transfer of personal information to countries outside of your country of residence, in particular to Japan and the United States.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. lf we make any changes, we will notify you by revising the "Last Updated" date at the top of this Privacy Policy and where appropriate we may provide you with additional notice (such as adding a statement to the log-in screen or sending you an email notification). Your continued use of our Services after the revised Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood, and agreed to the current version of this Policy. lf you do not agree to the Privacy Policy, do not use any Websites and Service.

### Contact Information

Please contact us with any questions or comments about this Policy, your personal information, or our use and disclosure practices by email at [privacy@pioneerdj.com](mailto:privacy@pioneerdj.com) or in writing at Pioneer DJ Corporation,6F, Yokohama i-Mark Place, 4-4-5 Minatomirai, Nishiku, Yokohama, Kanag awa, 220-0012 Japan.

lf you are located in the European Economic Area, Pioneer DJ Europe Limited may be the entity responsible for the processing your personal information. To contact us in the EU, please use the following contact details: Pioneer DJ Europe Limited, Artemis Building, Odyssey Business Park, West End Road, South Ruislip, Middlesex, HA4 6QE, England.

lf you are located in the United States, Pioneer DJ Americas, lnc. may be the entity responsible for the processing your personal information. To contact us in the United States, please use the following contact details: Pioneer DJ Americas, lnc. 2050 W 190th Street, Suite #109, Torrance, CA 90504, USA.
